# Andre Hidayatullah

dre.hidayatullah@gmail.com (+62) 85360094470 Jl. Madrasah Jakarta, Cengkareng

#### Summary

He's a passionate-individual with an entrepreneurial spirit that strives for exceptional customer service. Collaborative, skilled at nurturing positive, long-term client relationships to drive business growth, and ambitious learner focusing on sales expertise. Currently learning Copywriting and Web development for deeper understanding in the field of marketing.

### **Experience**

### Sales Marketing

PT Gaya Makmur Tractors • West Jakarta, Jakarta 09/2021 - Present

- Remind customers to replace spare parts for heavy equipment
- Offer spare parts to companies that have heavy equipment, especially heavy equipment made in Germany

### Marketing and Social Media Manager

Aceh Camera • Banda Aceh, Aceh 10/2018 - 08/2021

- · Develop an engaging content for increasing the sales
- Make ads for instagram and determine effective targets for ads
- Established company's first social media presence across Instagram
- · Managed and scaled a brand advocate for increasing customer

## Photographer and Social Media Manager

Senja Merupa Studio • Banda Aceh, Aceh 01/2020 - 08/2021

- Create professional visual images using various photography equipment and communicated with clients to determine their needs and goals
- Delivered finished products, and promoted the company's services and portfolio over the Instagram

#### **Skills**

- · Microsoft office
- Copywriting
- Design
- · Video Editing
- · Analytical Thinking
- · Adobe Illustrator

- Digital marketing
- Logical Thinking
- Photography
- · Customer care
- · Adobe Photoshop
- Social media marketing

### **Education**

## Mining engineering

Universitas Syiah Kuala • Banda Aceh, Aceh 11/2020

Graduated college with a GPA of 3.06/4.00 besides learning about mining, He's also learning how to manage organizations and learning design graphics using Adobe Illustrator and Adobe photoshop.

#### Languages

English

Indonesian